KISHAN PATEL

3302 28th Street, S, Lethbridge, AB TIK 2W1 403-635-7550 (cell) kishanpat2015@gmail.com (email)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced managerial skilled personnel capable of working in a fast-paced environment and performing the assigned duties and tasks as required. Experienced in problem solving and team work to achieve attainable goals and succeed. Passionate and talented to work with computers.

SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skill.
- Strong time management and organizational skills.
- Able to work under pressure with excellent multitasking abilities, energy, and efficiency.
- Able to problem solve, think critically, and resolve conflicts amicably.
- Ability to adapt to environmental and work changes.
- Pay attention to details and able to summarize reports or results accurately.
- Able to access the needs of individuals and develop appropriate client-centered solutions.
- Able to work with Microsoft Office packages.
- Ability to troubleshoot and resolve computer related problems.
- Ability to work with Java, C++, C#, HTML and JavaScript.

EXPERIENCE

Operational Manager

January 2020 – August 2021

Shri Gayatri Plastic Limited (Machakos, Kenya)

- Planning of the tasks of the day and ensure they are completed by the end of the day.
- Contact clients and take orders for goods and scheduling the transportation.
- Preparing and posting purchase order for raw materials for goods.
- Preparing payrolls and making payments to workers.
- Marketing and advertising of products to people.

Security Guard
Rhino Security Inc (Lethbridge, Alberta)

July 2022 - Current

- Guarding of people and property.
- Managing and directing of crowds.
- Reporting and resolving incidents encountered.
- Updating supervisors on hourly basis on the status at work.
- Submitting of reports after all shifts via the company's system.

EDUCATION

Lethbridge College, Lethbridge, AB, Canada Diploma in Computer Information Technology (Currently Enrolled)

Katoloni Secondary School, Machakos, Kenya Completed grade 9 to 12 (2016-2019)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Led a team to accomplish a project to build a progressive website that would allow users to share information for an organisation.

REFERENCES

Aisha Patel, Healthcare Practical Nurse – Lethbridge, Canada +1 (587) 257-8697

Sabtyain Mirza, Peace Officer & Healthcare Security Manager - Lethbridge, Canada +1 (306) 716-8944

Hitesh Chavda, Director and Manager Shri Gayatri Plastic Limited- Machakos, Kenya +(254) 702 787000